{
    "quizess": [
        {
            "level": 1,
            "Level_name": "Level 1",
            "content": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "levelContent": 1,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Aku",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Aku.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "levelContent": 1,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Kamu",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Kamu.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "levelContent": 1,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Dia",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Dia.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "levelContent": 1,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Kamu.mp4",
                    "options": ["Aku", "Ayah", "Kamu", "Dia"],
                    "answer": "Kamu"
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "levelContent": 1,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Dia.mp4",
                    "options": ["Kamu", "Dia", "Aku", "Ayah"],
                    "answer": "Dia"
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "levelContent": 1,
                    "type": "essay",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Aku.mp4",
                    "answer": "Aku"
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "levelContent": 1,
                    "type": "essay",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Dia.mp4",
                    "answer": "Dia"
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "levelContent": 1,
                    "type": "practice",
                    "question": "Peragakan gerakan ini!",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Kamu.mp4",
                    "answer": "Kamu"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": 2,
            "Level_name": "Level 2",
            "content": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Halo",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Halo.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Tolong",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Tolong.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Terima Kasih",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Terima%20kasih.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Halo.mp4",
                    "options": ["Halo", "Tolong", "Terima Kasih", "Permisi"],
                    "answer": "Halo"
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "essay",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Tolong.mp4",
                    "answer": "Tolong"
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-ganti-orang/Aku.mp4",
                    "options": ["Terima Kasih", "Halo", "Kamu", "Aku"],
                    "answer": "Aku"
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Terima%20kasih.mp4",
                    "options": ["Terima Kasih", "Halo", "Kamu", "Aku"],
                    "answer": "Terima Kasih"
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "essay",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Tolong.mp4",
                    "answer": "Tolong"
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "levelContent": 2,
                    "type": "practice",
                    "question": "Peragakan gerakan ini!",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Terima%20kasih.mp4",
                    "answer": "Terima Kasih"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": 3,
            "Level_name": "Level 3",
            "content": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Sama-sama",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Sama%20sama.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Maaf",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Maaf.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Jangan",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Jangan.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "essay",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Maaf.mp4",
                    "answer": "Maaf"
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Sama%20sama.mp4",
                    "options": ["Terima Kasih", "Sama-sama", "Maaf", "Jangan"],
                    "answer": "Sama-sama"
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "essay",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Jangan.mp4",
                    "answer": "Jangan"
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Terima%20kasih.mp4",
                    "options": ["Terima Kasih", "Sama-sama", "Maaf", "Jangan"],
                    "answer": "Terima Kasih"
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Jangan.mp4",
                    "options": ["Maaf", "Terima Kasih", "Jangan", "Sama-sama"],
                    "answer": "Jangan"
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "levelContent": 3,
                    "type": "practice",
                    "question": "Peragakan gerakan ini!",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Maaf.mp4",
                    "answer": "Maaf"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": 4,
            "Level_name": "Level 4",
            "content": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Sama-sama",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Sama%20sama.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Maaf",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Maaf.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "material",
                    "name": "Jangan",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Jangan.mp4"
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "essay",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Maaf.mp4",
                    "answer": "Maaf"
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Sama%20sama.mp4",
                    "options": ["Terima Kasih", "Sama-sama", "Maaf", "Jangan"],
                    "answer": "Sama-sama"
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "essay",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Jangan.mp4",
                    "answer": "Jangan"
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Terima%20kasih.mp4",
                    "options": ["Terima Kasih", "Sama-sama", "Maaf", "Jangan"],
                    "answer": "Terima Kasih"
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "multiple_choices",
                    "question": "Isyarat apakah ini?",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Jangan.mp4",
                    "options": ["Maaf", "Terima Kasih", "Jangan", "Sama-sama"],
                    "answer": "Jangan"
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "levelContent": 4,
                    "type": "practice",
                    "question": "Peragakan gerakan ini!",
                    "link": "https://storage.googleapis.com/vide-materi-signify/kata-sehari-hari/Maaf.mp4",
                    "answer": "Maaf"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
